fair.org 2016-06-09

# Privacy Policy | FAIR

### FAIR Privacy Policy

**Website Privacy  Policy**

FAIR is committed to your online privacy. FAIR servers may record the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software and operating system you use; the date and time you access our site; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site.

We use this information to measure the number of visitors to the site, to diagnose and correct system errors, and to improve the site. We delete this information after one month. We do not connect this information to your name or identity.

**Email List Privacy  Policy**

When you subscribe to FAIR’s email list, you will receive a confirmation message that you must respond to in order to activate your subscription. We will not add you to our list without your confirmation.

We will use your email address to send you updates, alerts and occasional event announcements. The subscriber list is kept confidential, so no need to worry about spammers. We will never sell or give your e-mail address to anyone.

You can unsubscribe at any time by sending a blank email message to the address that will appear at the end of every message you receive.

**Transactions and Online  Giving**

For all financial transactions, our site has been equipped with security measures to ensure the safest transactions possible. These measures will work to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of any data under FAIR’s control.

**Email List Privacy  Policy**

When you subscribe to FAIR’s email list, you will receive a confirmation message that you must respond to in order to activate your subscription. We will not add you to our list without your confirmation.

We will use your email address to send you updates, alerts and occasional event announcements. The subscriber list is kept confidential, so no need to worry about spammers. We will never sell or give your e-mail address to anyone.

You can unsubscribe at any time by sending a blank email message to the address that will appear at the end of every message you receive.

_FAIR Store Purchases_ : When purchasing products or subscriptions to _Extra!_ from the FAIR online store, any financial information you send to us will be saved with our banking records for verification of deposits and handling of refunds only.

_Online giving_ : Details of these online donation transactions, including personal information or giving history, will not be shared with any outside organization.

**_Extra!_ Privacy Policy**

FAIR well understands how hard it is for public interest groups, with limited resources, to get their message out. Occasionally, we share our list of subscribers to _Extra!_ —our print newsletter—with groups or publications we feel might be of interest to you. If you prefer that your name and address remain confidential, just let us know. Call us toll-free at 800-847-3993. To stop getting direct mail altogether go to:

https://www.dmachoice.org/register.php

For your convenience, here is the Do Not Call Registry link to stop receiving unwanted phone call (FAIR never uses phone services):

**https://www.donotcall.gov/Opt-Out  Policy**

We always offer you every possible opportunity to opt out of providing personal information. In cases where personal information is needed, e.g. web-based financial transactions, we will keep this information confidential.
